Hi everyone in today's video. I'm going to explain how the credit statement
works and how to work out what you've made on any given day
so first of all I've logged into my profile and
Now I'm going to go to my details credits
And click here on credit statement
Here is your credit statement this shows all of the transactions and all of the
credits that you've made
Since the very start of your webcam journey
So here this last page is the most recent
Transactions and most recent credits that you've made
So what we're going to do is today, I'm going to show you exactly how to work
out what you've made on any given day
I'm going to choose the 5th of August
So to work out what you've made on any given day
You need to subtract what you started on that day from what you ended on
So let's start on what we ended on
So if we want to work out what we made on the 5th of August, we will go to the
very last transaction on the 5th
which is here and
We're going to go along and see what what it was what we ended on
Okay, so as you can see here, we ended the 5th on
228.24 credits, so we're going to put that into our calculator
Okay, I've now put that into my calculator
Now I'm going to see what I started that day on
So as you can still see here, there's still transactions from the 5th here
So we need to go back a page to see if there are any more
So we just click this arrow to go back one page
So we need to find the 5th of the 8th here
We'll go down. We should be able to find it
Okay, there we go. There are a couple of transactions here on the 5th of the 8
th
So we just need the very first transaction
That's all we need to worry about and we just need to see what the balance was
at the very start of the day
So as we can see the balance is 8.55 credits, so now we need to subtract that
from the final balance
So I have a mark I have in my calculator
What we ended that day on and now I'm going to subtract 8.55 from that
So I have two to eight point two four take away eight point five five
And that equals
290 point 69 credits
So that's how many credits we made on the 5th and we're not finished yet
because this is how many credits you made
To now work out how much that is in pounds how much money you should expect in
your bank the next day
We now need to take away
43.5%
So I'm going to do that on my calculator now
So that leaves us with
124.12 pounds
So that's how much you should have in your bank the next day
So yes, it's very simple to work out. You just
Work out what you enter the day on
subtract what you start the day on and then whatever that remaining balances
take away
43.5% and that's how much pounds you've made that day
I'm now going to explain a couple more things on the credit statement
So as you can see here the balance goes down to zero and again here and it says
it's a group transfer
This basically is our payroll company transferring all of the credits out the
account
This happens every week or so. So don't worry about it. It may happen when you
're online
It may happen halfway through the week. It really doesn't matter and it's not
something that you need to worry about
The payroll company just have to transfer your credits out as obviously they
need to take the money out of the
in profile to then pay you
Here as well, it says available for transfer now
You don't need to worry about this either. You do not need to transfer your
credits or payroll company do everything for you
They work out how much you've made when to pay you how to pay you and
Everything that comes in between so you don't need to worry about this at all
You don't actually need to check or worry about your credits
At all because our payroll company like I said do everything for you and pay
you daily
But if you do want to check what you've made each day, you can just follow the
steps that I said earlier
One final thing to remember is that you have to earn 90 credits to be paid the
next day
If you don't earn 90 credits
They just sit in your balance until the next time that you work and then they
'll get paid the following day
And the day ends at 12 o'clock midnight, so bear that in mind when working out
how much you've made I
Hope all that makes sense, and if you have any more questions, please ask your
mental